Three years until the Great Invasion, huh?
I never practiced seriously
with a sword or magic.
So I'll need... Strength! Haste!
My spells are more effective?
Has my magic power increased?
I have more magic power than I used to,
but my body can't keep up.
Even with a suicide charge,
I'm dead in an instant.
Wait. It's all pointless if I die anyway.
I'm trying to get stronger so I can live
happily and healthily into old age.
What's gotten into him?
He's been acting weird since yesterday.
Just three days ago, he'd call it quits
after fifty staring contests in a row.
I won most of the time, of course.
I swear, you kids are always up to no good.
Welcome home, Miss Layla.
Hey, Mom.
Has my idiot son been providing for himself?
He came to beg me for food every day.
Hey, don't tell her that first thing.
You can give me the full story later.
What kind of monster is he fighting?
He's acting like a completely
different person.
Did something happen?
I know, right? Until the other day,
he had the eyes of a dead fish.
And said his dream was to screw
around with his inheritance.
There's only one thing that would make
a kid like him change overnight.
A woman.
A-A woman?
Guess it wasn't her.
Damn him. He beat me to it.
If that's how our likely suspect responds,
maybe I'm wrong.
My back is burning for some reason.
Is this also an effect of my
increased magic power?
Yikes...
Confess. Who is it?
Wh-What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb! Who are
you messing around with?!
Hey! What are you doing?
Calm down!
Who is it? Come on!
What are you—
Who was it? Who?! Come on!
Sorry about earlier.
To make up for it,
I made an extra-nice lunch.
Help yourself to this too.
Hey, whoa, this is pretty decadent!
Anyway, so you're back, Master?
Good to see you again, Layla.
Since my master's here now,
there's something I'd like to ask all of you.
Why so formal?
Who do you think could exert influence
and bend the ear of multiple nations?
What kind of question is that?
Bend the ear of nations, huh?
A king or something, maybe?
The highest-ranking priests of Earth
Mother Kairis have influence as well.
There's also...
Randolph the hero.
The one who defeated the demon king
in the war three hundred years ago.
Yeah. Even elves and dwarves,
not just humans, might listen to him.
So kings, high priests, and heroes, huh?
Of those, the only one
I could be in two years is...
a hero.
Which means I have no choice
but to become a hero.
Something has to have happened, right?
I don't see the problem.
He's thinking about the future now.
We should watch over him
with care for now.
Not like we have a choice.
What gives? My back is burning again.
Knowing what's coming
is certainly an advantage.
I'm glad I have a good memory.
Whoa, this is impressive.
I've never been so grateful
my mom's such a bookworm.
Are you serious about trying to become a hero?
Of course. As quickly as possible too.
But it's not like that's something
you can just go out and do.
I know. Got any good ideas for me?
How about defeating the demon king?
If I could do that, I wouldn't be stuck.
Yeah, I guess not.
What do you think a hero needs?
Strength, right?
That's a given, but strength
alone is meaningless.
Then what else does a hero need?
First, I think they need money.
Well, that's oddly blunt.
A hero doesn't accept rewards
for helping people.
That said, traveling
and adventuring cost money.
Yeah, you can't do either
without funds to spare.
Next, a hero needs connections.
Receiving special treatment
from the famous and influential
naturally increases your own renown.
This is starting to sound shady.
You can do most things
with money and connections.
But that's still not enough.
What else do you need?
A hero also needs luck.
Luck, huh?
Yes, but not just any kind of luck.
Gotta be in the right place
when misfortune strikes.
Then you step in and become a hero.
Wait a minute. You don't mean...
No, I'm not talking about creating
problems so I can solve them myself.
In any case, I intend to use all means
available, even if they're underhanded.
That doesn't sound like something
an aspiring hero would say.
Why do you even want to be one, anyway?
You're curious?
When I look at you, it doesn't feel
like becoming a hero is your real goal.
It's like that's a step on your way
to achieving something.
I do have my reasons, but you'll
just have to trust me, friend.
If you say so, then fine.
Good luck. I'll be rooting for you.
Actually, I expect you to help me.
Now, I can use this for funds,
and I'd like to meet her again soon.
As for renown, if I can do something
about the Archen incident...
I'll be cutting it close, though.
Going on a journey, eh?
This is rather sudden.
Have you told Ceraia?
Yes. She cried a bit.
Well, she's overprotective.
What did you tell Lauer?
Well, learning more
about the world is a good thing.
Take this guy with you.
What?
I intended to, but I'm glad
to have your permission.
He makes a good shield.
I wouldn't waste him like that.
I need a sacrificial pawn.
Does what I want not matter? How could you?
Is it true you're going on a journey?
Yeah, in two days.
Where are you going?
My first stop is Malad, the royal capital.
I'll get what I need there,
and then the real work can begin.
Listen, Kyle...
I'm not taking you with me.
Why not? You're taking Theron, aren't you?
I train with the Oracle Warriors!
I won't get in your way!
I doubt your mother would want
you to put yourself in danger.
I'll apologize at her grave
as much as I have to.
I want you to stay someplace safe too.
But I—
When I return, you'll be
the first person I come see.
So have faith and wait for me.
No fair.
I can't say anything when you pull that.
Call it the composure that comes with age.
What are you talking about?
We're both sixteen.
Promise me you'll come back safe, okay?
Yeah. I won't do anything reckless.
Okay.
Sorry for making you come shopping with me.
Nah, I don't mind at all.
Oh, an elf.
How unusual.
She's so pretty.
Kyle?
Kyle...
When we're alone together,
call me by my true name.
My true name is—
Eksess.
What did you just say?
Oh, uh...
Crap. We're just meeting for the first time.
Worse, that name is a secret!
Just who are you?
Wait!
What are you doing? Let go of me!
She's going to make a scene.
I have no choice.
Sleep, Eksess!
H-How dare you...
Come to think of it, she did mention
she'd been to Rimarzé before.
Never expected to run into her here.
Kyle, I know she's beautiful, but I can't
believe you'd make a move on her so quickly.
I-I can explain all this.
See, I was lonely without you...
What are you talking about?!
You have me right here!
Okay, I'm going with you after all!
And you can't stop me!
Uh, nice to meet you.
It's Miss Urza, right?
You think that'll work now?
Only my parents and I know my true name!
Where and how did you learn it?
Oh, uh...
I can't tell her that, four years from now,
we'll fall in love and she'll
share it with me herself...
Normally, I'd have to kill you
to keep you silent.
H-Hang on...
I'll tell you eventually.
Don't be absurd!
Have you any idea how important
an elf's true name is?
I do, but I can't let you kill me.
So I have a suggestion.
Until I can tell you, why don't
we do an Application of the Contract
to prevent me from using
your true name for evil?
You know about the
Application of the Contract?
Usually, contracts are forged with spirits,
but in the name of deities,
elementalers can give their
true name to bind human beings.
The terms will be that I won't tell anyone
your true name or use it for ill.
How does that sound?
You know what happens
if you break the contract, yes?
Yeah. I'll die.
My life is hanging in the balance as well.
If you're serious, let's do it.
Very well.
That said, I cannot currently forge
the contract unless the moon is full.
The next full moon is a few weeks away.
We'll have to stay here in town until then.
Oh, sorry. I'm actually leaving tomorrow.
C-Come again?
Kyle, you can't just eat meat, okay?
I know, Mom.
Don't worry. I'll be with him.
You're really coming?
Of course. That's already settled.
Good luck, Kyle. And make sure
you watch out for your friends.
He's talking to you, you know?
Right.
Even my dad's here?
Well, Mom, Dad... take care of yourselves.
Don't stay up all night reading.
Okay.
I'll be back.
We'll be back!
I'm delighted a beauty like you
decided to join our party.
I'm just here to watch him.
I'm not part of your party.
Wait, isn't the royal capital the other way?
We can save that for later
now that Urza the elementaler
has joined our party.
I-I told you, I'm not in your party.
First, we make for the Sungard Mountains.
Do you know the Legend of Sungard?
Isn't that about the ancient
magic kingdom of Xarles?
It's about the Magic Queen's Labyrinth, right?
That place is just a legend.
Actually...
I have here a map of the place.
It even shows the treasure room.
Kyle...
You poor thing. You got scammed with a fake.
No! I swear it's real!
Right. Of course you want to believe that.
People who become obsessed
with money always end up unhappy.
Yeah, I guess it's too much
to expect them to buy in like that.
This map...
It's made from a magic tree
over a thousand years old.
The technology has long been lost,
so these can no longer be produced.
It's most likely genuine.
What? Really?
Then it's gotta be the real deal.
You can always trust what
a beautiful woman says.
These jerks...
But this place looks massive.
How long will it take to reach the treasure?
Don't worry. I have a plan.
Which is?
We'll dig.
Why are we digging a tunnel?
I told you, we're digging a
shortcut to the treasure.
The labyrinth is huge
and full of dangerous traps.
Traps?
There are lots of riddles too.
Riddles?
There are even autonomous magic weapons.
Magic weapons?!
Was all that stuff on the map?
Uh, actually...
I know they're there because of all
the trouble they gave me last time.
This labyrinth is the stuff of legend.
We have to be on our guard.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
When I swore to become a hero,
I didn't think digging a tunnel
would be the first thing I'd do.
I could say the same thing.
Why are we using a gnome spirit to do this?
Hey, it's saving us the cost
of buying magic equipment.
Theron, don't dig there yet.
I haven't finished reinforcing the walls.
What? Really?
And Kyle, use Detect Magic to confirm
the direction of the treasure room.
I'm already on it.
Is it just me, or does Urza
seem the most into this?
Well, she's a serious girl.
No chatting!
Yes, ma'am!
That's good!
Food tastes even better after hard labor.
It's revitalizing after the effort
I spent on spirit magic too.
Have as much as you'd like.
Did you catch this, Liese?
Yup.
With a trap or something?
My bare hands.
Your hands?
I never dreamed I'd get to take a
bath so deep in the mountains.
You made this, didn't you, Miss Urza?
Yes. I had an undine provide groundwater.
I devised this little trick for long journeys.
Magic is so nifty.
I'm jealous since I can't use any.
Felling a bear with your bare
hands is far more impressive.
Did you get so strong for Kyle's sake?
I guess so, although I felt
I needed it for myself too.
Miss Urza, I don't think you need to worry
about your true name too much.
I know Kyle's hiding something.
But he'd never do anything to make us cry.
So I plan to wait until he tells us what it is.
Right.
If he does anything to hurt you,
Miss Urza, I'll take responsibility and...
Call me Urza.
Huh?
You don't need to call me "miss."
Okay, Urza.
A heart...
Don't mention that!
I'm self-conscious about it!
You're so cute, Urza!
Let go of me! I'm gonna go spy on them!
Don't! I can't allow you to see them naked!
We're almost there.
Theron's not back yet?
Nah, he said he was taking a break.
He always does this.
No matter. I have a question for you.
Why do you want to become a hero?
Liese and Theron won't pry because
they trust you, but I'm different.
Those rings are part of your
training, aren't they?
You noticed?
Each one of these increases my
body weight by two or three times.
In any case, for now, I'm trying
to work on my physical fitness.
Why go so far?
Does it have anything to do
with you knowing my true name?
Well...
We made it!
Go fetch Liese and Theron!
G-Got it.
This is...
Incredible.
All right.
For real?
You could fool around for a lifetime
and still have money left over!
Yahoo!
Keep your wits about you.
We're only here because I need
money to achieve my goal.
Don't become a slave to it.
Y-You're right.
You're not wrong.
Look. That's what happens to people
who become obsessed with money!
Yahoo!
Money, money, money!
I'm rich!
How disgraceful.
I'm gonna spend this on so many women!
No one wants to end up like that.
Thank you, Theron.
Because of you, their hearts will remain pure.
Yahoo! Money, money, money!
It's all mine!
Now's my chance.
A human, eh?
I'm impressed you made it this far.
Next Time
Application of the Contract
Next time: "Application of the Contract."